Christine KiyabuUI Designer

https://christinek2.github.io/portfolio-website/

Los Angeles, CA

Contact Details

christine.s.kiyabu@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/christinese-k Languages: English & Japanese

EDUCATION

UI/UX Design Certificate | 2020

CareerFoundry

- 10 month/500+ hours intensive project-based training program with industry-leading mentors. Studies spanned from visual design principles, color theory, grids, and UI/UX best practices to wireframing, prototyping, responsive design, mobile gestures, and animated interactions.
- Student Projects https://christinek2.github.io/portfolio-website/
 Unfiltered You: iOS Mobile Online Skincare Product Store App
 TrackHere: iOS & Android Mobile Package Tracking Aggregator App
 Designed an iOS mobile app for a skincare product store through the
 process of competitor analysis, user flows, user testing, iteration,
 branding, wireframing, and prototyping.

Cosmetology License | 2015

KC Beauty Academy

BA Psychology | 2012

University of California, Santa Barbara

PROFILE

Accurately assesses individual's needs and creates aesthetically functional UI design by combining both the fascination for the human response with an eye for creativity.

Diverse background, ranging from a psychology degree and experience in sales strategy, to a creative and visual design-focused background in cosmetology and wedding planning.

TOOLS

- Sketch
- Photoshop
- InVision
- Marvel
- Flinto
- Balsamiq
- GitHub
- Atom
- UsabilityHub
- Microsoft Office

DESIGN SKILLS-

- Web & Mobile Design
- Wireframing
- Branding/Visual Design
- Usability & A/B Testing
- Storytelling
- User Research
- User Flows
- User Personas
- Style Guides
- Prototyping

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing & Sales Assistant | Feb 2021 - Present
Sales Strategy Administrative Assistant | Apr 2018 - Jan 2021

Wismettac Asian Foods Inc (Santa Fe Springs, CA)

- Increase customer acquisition and brand awareness through the creation of marketing materials such as sell sheets, brochures, trade show materials, packages, etc.
- Conduct market research to identify and analyze consumer behavior

Behavioral Therapist | May 2016 - May 2017

Center for Autism & Related Disorders (Los Angeles, CA)

• Implemented behavioral intervention programs to prompt interactive success

Bridal Hair & Makeup Artist | Jan 2016 - May 2017

Kelly Zhang Studio (Pasadena, CA)

• Performed professional bridal makeup on 150+ clients

Wedding Planner | Jul 2013 - Nov 2013

Kanalu Wedding (Honolulu, HI)

• Multi-tasked to organize and plan every aspect of client weddings, from creating financial estimates to coordinating with multiple vendors